let uscapitals = {
	detail: {
		title: 'State Capitals',
		shuffle: [-1, -1, 5, 5, 0],
		showQuestion: true,
	},
	cards: [
		{
			front: 'Alabama',
			back: 'Montgomery',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Alaska',
			back: 'Juneau',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Arizona',
			back: 'Phoenix',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Arkansas',
			back: 'Little Rock',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'California',
			back: 'Sacramento',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Colorado',
			back: 'Denver',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Connecticut',
			back: 'Hartford',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Delaware',
			back: 'Dover',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Florida',
			back: 'Tallahassee',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Georgia',
			back: 'Atlanta',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Hawaii',
			back: 'Honolulu',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Idaho',
			back: 'Boise',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Illinois',
			back: 'Springfield',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Indiana',
			back: 'Indianapolis',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Iowa',
			back: 'Des Moines',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Kansas',
			back: 'Topeka',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Kentucky',
			back: 'Frankfort',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Louisiana',
			back: 'Baton Rouge',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Maine',
			back: 'Augusta',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Maryland',
			back: 'Annapolis',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Massachusetts',
			back: 'Boston',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Michigan',
			back: 'Lansing',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Minnesota',
			back: 'Saint Paul',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Mississippi',
			back: 'Jackson',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Missouri',
			back: 'Jefferson City',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Montana',
			back: 'Helena',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Nebraska',
			back: 'Lincoln',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Nevada',
			back: 'Carson City',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'New Hampshire',
			back: 'Concord',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'New Jersey',
			back: 'Trenton',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'New Mexico',
			back: 'Santa Fe',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'New York',
			back: 'Albany',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'North Carolina',
			back: 'Raleigh',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'North Dakota',
			back: 'Bismark',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Ohio',
			back: 'Columbus',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Oklahoma',
			back: 'Oklahoma City',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Oregon',
			back: 'Salem',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Pennsylvania',
			back: 'Harrisburg',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Rhode Island',
			back: 'Providence',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'South Carolina',
			back: 'Columbia',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'South Dakota',
			back: 'Pierre',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Tennessee',
			back: 'Nashville',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Texas',
			back: 'Austin',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Utah',
			back: 'Salt Lake City',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Vermont',
			back: 'Montpelier',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Virginia',
			back: 'Richmond',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Washington',
			back: 'Olympia',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'West Virginia',
			back: 'Charleston',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Wisconsin',
			back: 'Madison',
			score: 1,
		},
		{
			front: 'Wyoming',
			back: 'Cheyenne',
			score: 1,
		},
	],
};
